[
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Choose the correct alternative to complete the sentence. “ He – to see us if he had been able to”",
    "options": ["would come", "would have come", "may have come", "bad attack"],
    "answer": "would have come"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "Choose the appropriate alternative to complete the sentence. He had a -- of fever.",
    "options": [
      "strong attack",
      "severe attack",
      "serious attack",
      "bad attack"
    ],
    "answer": "severe attack"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Choose the correct sentence.",
    "options": [
      "I asked Javed had he passed",
      "I asked Javed that had he passed",
      "I asked Javed if you had passed",
      "I asked Javed if he had passed"
    ],
    "answer": "I asked Javed if he had passed"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Choose the correct sentence.",
    "options": [
      "A few of the three boys got a prize",
      "All of the three boys got a prize",
      "Each of the three boys got a prize",
      "Each of the three boy got a prize"
    ],
    "answer": "Each of the three boys got a prize"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Choose the correct sentence.",
    "options": [
      "The man that said that was a fool",
      "The man who said that was a fool.",
      "The man that said that was a fool.",
      "The man which said that was a fool."
    ],
    "answer": "The man who said that was a fool."
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Choose the correct answer. How long did you wait?",
    "options": [
      "Till lunch time",
      "Till he came",
      "Untill 6 o'clock",
      "since this morning"
    ],
    "answer": "Till he came"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "\"What will be the correct preposition to complete the sentence? \"\"I am not bad.... tennis.\"\"",
    "options": ["about", "with", "in", "at"],
    "answer": "at"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What is the antonym of ''Gentle''?",
    "options": ["foolish", "modest", "clever", "rude"],
    "answer": "rude"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What is the synonym of 'Jovial?",
    "options": ["Jolly", "Jealous", "Gay", "Happy"],
    "answer": "Jolly"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What is the synonym of 'competent' ?",
    "options": ["circumspect", "discrete", "capable", "prudent"],
    "answer": "capable"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "\"Who is the auther of \"\"A Farewell to Arms\"\"?\"",
    "options": [
      "Ernest Hemingway",
      "Thomas Hardy",
      "George Orwel",
      "H. G. Wells"
    ],
    "answer": "Ernest Hemingway"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "\"Who is the auther of \"\"Animal Farm\"\"?\"",
    "options": [
      "George Orwel",
      "Thomas More",
      "Boris Pasternak",
      "Charles Dickens"
    ],
    "answer": "George Orwel"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "\"Who is the author of \"\"India Wins Freedom\"\"?\"",
    "options": [
      "Mahatma Gandhi",
      "J. L. Nehru",
      "Abul Kalam Azad",
      "Debashish"
    ],
    "answer": "Abul Kalam Azad"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "\"what kind of noun is \"\"Cattle\"\"?\"",
    "options": ["Collective", "Common", "Material", "Proper"],
    "answer": "Collective"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "What kind of noun is girl ?",
    "options": ["Collective", "Proper", "Common", "Material"],
    "answer": "Common"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "What is the meaning of 'White Elephant'?",
    "options": [
      "A very costly or troublesome possession",
      "A black marketer",
      "A hoarder",
      "An elephant of white colour"
    ],
    "answer": "A very costly or troublesome possession"
  }
]
